(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
ホロライブ1期生 7周年記念！
Hololive 1st Generation 7th Anniversary!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
いっせーの！
Ready, set, go!
電脳ぴゅあ推し大宣言！
Cyber Pure Love Declaration!
大好きを叫べ！
Shout out your love!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
君のハートに 届け
Let it reach your heart
ぴゅあぴゅあな愛を！
With pure, pure love!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ずっと隣に いたいよ
I want to stay by your side forever
約束だよ
It's a promise
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
いっせーの！
Ready, set, go!
電脳ぴゅあ推し大宣言！
Cyber Pure Love Declaration!
大好きを叫べ！
Shout out your love!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
君のハートに 届け
Let it reach your heart
ぴゅあぴゅあな愛を！
With pure, pure love!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ずっと隣に いたいよ
I want to stay by your side forever
約束だよ
It's a promise
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
いっせーの！
Ready, set, go!
電脳ぴゅあ推し大宣言！
Cyber Pure Love Declaration!
大好きを叫べ！
Shout out your love!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
君のハートに 届け
Let it reach your heart
ぴゅあぴゅあな愛を！
With pure, pure love!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ずっと隣に いたいよ
I want to stay by your side forever
約束だよ
It's a promise
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
いっせーの！
Ready, set, go!
電脳ぴゅあ推し大宣言！
Cyber Pure Love Declaration!
大好きを叫べ！
Shout out your love!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
君のハートに 届け
Let it reach your heart
ぴゅあぴゅあな愛を！
With pure, pure love!
1st generation 電脳ぴゅあ推し大宣言
1st Generation: Denno Pure Oshi Daiseigen
月夜のセレナーデ
Serenade on a moonlit night
白い薔薇は誰を想う
Who does the white rose think of?
その身を綻ばせて
Letting its petals bloom
愛を歌うの
Singing of love
こぼれ落ちた 花びらが
The petals that fell off
寂しさのあとを隠した
Hid the traces of loneliness
ねえ早く迎えにきて
Hey, come to pick me up soon
最後の一枚が落ちる その前に
Before the last petal falls
今はどんな花とも群れないの
I won't mingle with any flower now
あなただけを待ってる
I'm only waiting for you
あなたとなら この身体が
If it's with you, even if this body
壊されたってかまわない
Is broken, I don't care
棘に触れたら傷つくわ
You'll get hurt if you touch the thorns
その覚悟がないなら
If you don't have that resolve
いっそここから消えてよ
Then just disappear from here
重く閉ざした So Secret Garden
Heavily closed, So Secret Garden
夜風はリゾルート
The night wind is resolute
白い薔薇は覚醒する
The white rose awakens
背中押されるように
As if being pushed forward
扉開いた
The door opened
ただ一人で枯れてゆくの
Will I just wither away all alone?
待ってるだけじゃいられない
I can't just keep waiting
衝動の赴くまま
Following my impulses
茨の道を裸足で駆け抜けてく
Running through the thorny path barefoot
凛と咲き誇る花でありたい
I want to be a flower blooming proudly
あなただけを求めて
Seeking only you
会いに行くの どんな遠く
I'm going to see you, no matter how far
離れていても見つけ出せる
Even if we're apart, I can find you
暗い世界も怖くない
I'm not afraid of the dark world
あなたを感じるから
Because I feel you
全て失ったっていい
It's fine even if I lose everything
二度と戻らない So Secret Garden
I'll never go back, So Secret Garden
今はどんな花とも群れないの
I won't mingle with any flower now
あなただけを求めて
Seeking only you
霞の向こう 私を呼ぶ
Beyond the mist, you call me
鮮やかに燃える 強気なバラ
A strong rose burning vividly
凛と咲き誇る花でありたい
I want to be a flower blooming proudly
やっとここで出会えた
Finally, we met here
あなたとなら この身体が
If it's with you, even if this body
壊されたってかまわない
Is broken, I don't care
棘に触れたら傷つくわ
You'll get hurt if you touch the thorns
その覚悟があるのね
You have that resolve, don't you?
手を取り合えば広がる
If we hold hands, it will expand
誰も知らない So Sacred Universe
The So Sacred Universe that no one knows
イェーイ！ 終わりましたー！
Yay! It's over!
ホロライブ1期生7周年ー！
Hololive 1st Generation 7th Anniversary!
さてじゃあちょっとね、Secret Garden 歌った後なんですけども
Now then, after singing Secret Garden...
まずは自己紹介！ 7年目の自己紹介！
First, self-introductions! Self-introductions for the 7th year!
はい！ やっていきますか。じゃあアキロゼから。
Yes! Let's do it. Then, starting with Akirose.
はーい！ 7年目の自己紹介いきます！
Heeey! Here goes the 7th year self-introduction!
ホロライブ1期生の癒し系ハーフエルフ、アキロゼこと
Hololive 1st Gen's healing half-elf, Akirose, aka
アキロゼんたーるです！ ハロハロハロ！ アローナ！
Aki Rosenthal! Hello hello hello! Alona!
アローナ！
Alona!
そして！
And!
はい、白上です。おしゃーす。
Yes, I'm Shirakami. Oshaasu.
あれ？ なんかすごいコンプリートだった。
Huh? That was a very complete self-introduction.
いつもシンプル。
Always simple.
こんにちは！
Hello!
こんこんこんきつね！白上フブキです！
Kon-kon-kon-fox! This is Shirakami Fubuki!
やったぜ！1期生7周年だ！
We did it! It's the 1st generation's 7th anniversary!
やったー！夜空メルです！
Yay! I'm Yozora Mel!
やめてくれ！やめてくれ！
Stop it! Stop it!
最近普通に自己紹介するの恥ずかしくなっちゃった...
Lately, it's gotten embarrassing to do a normal intro...
なんでだよ！恥を捨てろ！
Why?! Throw away your shame!
いや無理無理無理！
No, no way!
じゃ、そんな恥を捨てたはあちゃま！
Then, here's Haachama who threw away her shame!
見せてあげてよ！はあちゃまっちゃまー！
Show them! Haachama-chama!
最強アイドルの、はあちゃまこと赤井はあとです！
The strongest idol, Haachama, Akai Haato!
お世話になります！イエーイ！
Thank you for your support! Yay!
清楚担当、みんなのアイドル、夏色まつりです！
The purity rep, everyone's idol, Natsuiro Matsuri!
清楚？清楚？清楚？
Pure? Pure? Pure?
7年目も清楚にやってくぜ！
I'll keep being pure in our 7th year too!
最近ね、最近だいぶ落ち着きを取り戻して...
Lately, I've regained quite a bit of composure...
1曲目「Secret Garden」だったんですが...
The first song was "Secret Garden," but...
去年の周年で発表したオリ曲ということで...
Since it was the original song from last year...
あれから1年経ちました！
One year has passed since then!
早い！
So fast!
あの楽曲からもう1年。
A year already since that song.
いや早いね！
Yeah, it's fast!
あっという間だよ！秒、秒、秒だよ！
It was over in a flash! Seconds, seconds!
本当に秒すぎる！
It really was too fast!
今回はオープニングとして歌わせていただきましたが...
This time we sang it as the opening, but...
今年はオリ曲どうなんですか、はあとちゃん？
What about original songs this year, Haato-chan?
どうなんだろうね？
I wonder?
それは最後まで見てくれたら分かっちゃうかも！
You might find out if you watch until the end!
さあ、そしてそして！
Now, then!
なにやらステージが... 見てくださいよ！
The stage is... look at it!
おおー！すごーい！どこだここ？
Wow! Amazing! Where is this?
サイバーサイバー！
Cyber, cyber!
今回のステージはバーチャル世界の秋葉をイメージして！
This stage is modeled after virtual Akiba!
VTuberならではのデジタル感とか...
That digital feel unique to VTubers...
あとはなんかちょっと推し活感みたいな雰囲気もあって...
And there's also that "oshi-katsu" vibe...
そしてYAGO！YAGOやめて！
And YAGO! Stop it with YAGO!
一番光ってるよな！
He's the one shining the brightest!
ね！1号店、2号店あるし！
Right! There's a Shop 1 and Shop 2!
もうもろ秋葉だよ！
It's totally Akiba!
みんなのね、結構いろんな思い出の物たちがね、
A lot of everyone's memories are...
いろんなところに散りばめられてるんだよ！
scattered all over the place!
かっこよくて可愛いようなイメージとなっております。
It's designed to be both cool and cute.
そちらもぜひ堪能してください！
Please enjoy that as well!
そしてさらに！今回のハッシュタグは... こちら！
Furthermore! This time's hashtag is... this!
「#電脳ぴゅあ推し大宣言」！
#Cyber Pure Oshidai Sengen!
スクショ、感想いっぱいXでポストしてくれるよね？
You'll post screenshots and impressions on X, right?
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
ちなみにこのハッシュタグですが、なぜこの名前かは...
By the way, as for why it has this name...
最後まで見てくれたらその秘密が分かっちゃうかも！
You might find out the secret if you watch to the end!
本当に？分からなかった場合はどうしたらいい？
Really? What should we do if we don't get it?
はあちゃまが責任を取ります！
Haachama will take responsibility!
ありがとう！なんでもするって？
Thanks! You'll do anything?
なんでもする... いや、マジマジマジ！
Do anything... wait, seriously?!
ということで、いろいろ歌っていきたいんですが...
So, we'd like to sing various songs, but...
まずはですね、ソロパートからやっていこうと思います！
First, we'll start with the solo parts!
ソロの順番はもうあらかじめ発表しちゃいますか？
Should we announce the solo order beforehand?
1曲目歌う人！
The person singing the first song!
はい！まつりちゃん！
Me! Matsuri-chan!
まつりちゃんのソロはどんな感じなんですか？
What's Matsuri-chan's solo like?
この雰囲気に合った曲を選んだので楽しみに！
I chose a song that fits the vibe, so look forward!
そしてその次は？
And after that?
はい！はあとちゃん！
Me! Haato-chan!
はあとちゃんはどんな感じですか？
How about you, Haato-chan?
もりもりで行きましたのでお楽しみに！新曲もあるかも！
I went all out, so look forward! A new song too!
えーっ？！かも？！
Ehh?! Might?!
そしてその次が？
And next?
はい！メルです！
Me! Mel!
どんな感じの曲ですか？
What kind of song is it?
この空間にぴったりで、新世界みたいな！
It fits this space perfectly, like a new world!
新世界？地球？
New world? Earth?
ちょっとデカい感じでいかせていただきます！
I'll go with a grand feeling!
最後、白上は自分の好きな楽曲を歌わせていただきます。
Finally, I'll sing a song I really love.
なにやら騒がしい予感がしますので、お楽しみに！
I have a feeling it'll be noisy, so look forward!
トップバッターとしてまつりちゃん、いかせていただきます！
As the top batter, Matsuri-chan, take it away!
それではいきましょう！どうぞ！
Then, let's go! Please enjoy!
アンハッピー？
Unhappy?
悩める人の子よ
You troubled child
アンラッキー？
Unlucky?
人ならざるものも
Even those who aren't human
ビーハッピー！
Be happy!
たゆまず目指せよ
Keep aiming without stopping
アンデッド！
Undead!
生きていんだし
You're alive, after all
目を逸らした過去も
The past you looked away from
退屈な未来も
The boring future too
君もカウンセリング
You too, counseling
やれやれここらで
Well, well, around here
古今東西
In all times and places
ピースピース
Peace, peace
アンハッピー？
Unhappy?
アンラッキー？
Unlucky?
ビーハッピー！
Be happy!
アンデッド！
Undead!
ね ね ね ね
Hey, hey, hey, hey
なんだかんだして
Doing this and that
戦ってるようなそんな気がするの
I feel like I'm fighting
触れられない 触れたくもない
Can't be touched, don't even want to touch
過去の自分 自分 自分
My past self, self, self...
もう疾うに死んでる
I'm already long dead
透明な亡霊と対決
Facing off against a transparent ghost
幼気で痛い記憶の奥
Deep within innocent, painful memories
残念？もういないのに
Disappointing? Even though I'm no longer here
あれ？そっちがアイロニー
Huh? That's the irony
透かされているのは現在の自分？
Is the one being seen through the current me?
ナンセンス 消えないレッテル
Nonsense, an indelible label
Yes! 実はコンプレックスに取り憑かれているみたい
Yes! I seem to be possessed by my complexes
巻き付いたまま
Still wound around me,
まだ離れない
still won't leave
ありし日の自分
my past self
アンデッド！
Undead!
死んじゃいない お前とお前の連鎖
Not dead, the chain of you and you
生きてることは変わり続けることだ
To live is to keep changing
不幸に甘んじて満足するなよ
Don't be satisfied with being unhappy
幸せにならんとなんてよーだ
As if saying you won't become happy
この世はこの世は奇怪奇怪ファンタジー
This world, this world is a strange fantasy
次は鬼が出るか蛇が出るか
Next, will it be a demon or a snake?
出会って会ってやっと始まる物語
The story finally starts after meeting and meeting
さあ人か化け物か
Now, human or monster?
閑話休題 ピースピース
Digression aside, peace peace
Past & Future can't change the Past / run for the Future
何だかどうして未来になんぞ何の希望もないような気がして
Somehow I feel like there's no hope for the future
もう随分生きてる 既視感とテンプレ食傷
I've lived long enough to be sick of templates
素敵な出来事の気配もない
No sign of any wonderful events
積んだ経験の因果が形骸化だし今は退屈な進化
Past experiences have hollowed out into boredom
要は刺激が欲しいんだ
Basically, I want stimulation
飽きちゃった 慣れちゃった
Got tired of it, got used to it
ナンセンス 整っていくガイダンス
Nonsense, the guidance is being set
増えるコンプライアンス
Increasing compliance
蓋されていくみたい
Feels like I'm being shut in
吸い尽くして
Drain it all
あれも これも どれも 同じ味がする
That, this, which, they all taste the same
アンデッド！
Undead!
死んじゃいない お前とお前の連鎖
Not dead, the chain of you and you
いつの世も 過去も未来も今にあるんだ
In any age, the past and future are in the now
生きてることを 愚直に果たせよ
Fulfill your life with straightforwardness
目指せハッピーエンド
Aim for a happy ending
アンデッド！
Undead!
死んじゃいない お前に言ってるんだ
Not dead, I'm talking to you
幸せをひらめいてしまえよ 人であれ
Awaken to happiness, be a human
ただ苦しみに慣れて耐えているだけじゃ
If you just get used to and endure the pain...
死んでいるのと同義 屍のアンデッド
it's as if you're dead, an undead corpse
アンハッピー？悩める人の子よ
Unhappy? You suffering child of man
アンラッキー？人間になれるかも
Unlucky? You might become human
ビーハッピー！目を覚ましてよ
Be happy! Wake up
生きてるんだろう？
You're alive, aren't you?
不幸に浸るも 幸せになるのも
Wallowing in misfortune or becoming happy,
全部全部お前だ
it's all entirely up to you
東西一切合切森羅万象ピースピース
Everything in existence, peace peace
Past & Future can't change the Past / run for the Future
人の在る所に温もりありて
Where there are people, there is warmth
生き抜けこの化け物は語り草
Survive, this monster is a legend
清く 正しく 美しく
Pure, righteous, beautiful
8年目からは、キレイな赤井はあとに戻ることを
From my 8th year, I will return to being a clean Akai Haato...
私は 誓います
...I swear it
な～んて言うと思ったか!?
Did you really think I'd say that!?
いくぜーのみんな！
Let's go, everyone!
100周年までぶっ飛ばして
Keep pushing until the 100th anniversary
止まんないよな！
Don't stop!
イエス、ハイ！
Yes, high!
I just wanna live honestly
雑音ばかり
Nothing but noise
That's alright I'm gonna leave leave leave
Every time I say what
静観してなよ優等生は
Just watch from the sidelines, you goody-goody
Fake up 正義の味方
Fake up, ally of justice
Isn't it?
You must be good guy
You must be a good guy
Do as I told you
I'm sick of hearing
I ain't so good guy
I ain't such a good guy
Never be lap dog
Never be a lap dog
正論“的”なのもういいって
Enough with the 'logical' stuff already
「物語に必要」と
Saying 'it's necessary for the story'
そこまで言うのなら演じ切ってやるわ
If you go that far, I'll play the part perfectly
いい子ちゃんのまま
Staying a good child
Yes, Yes, Yes
No, No, No
Who is the Villain?
だって I'm a Hero, right?
Because I'm a Hero, right?
イヤになるわ
I'm sick of it
誰が正義なんて決めたのかしらね
I wonder who decided what justice is
もうどっちだって そういい子ちゃんのままじゃ
Either way, just staying a good girl...
はいちゃんちゃん！ Yeah
Haichan chan! Yeah
Who is the Villain?
One, two, three, go!
I give you my big RED HEART / My my big RED HEART
I'll be true to my RED HEART
My my big RED HEART / My my big RED HEART
I give you my big RED HEART
My my RED HEART / Big RED HEART
I'll be true to my RED HEART
My my big RED HEART / My my big RED HEART
いっただっきまーす
I'm digging in!
ドントカドン！ ドントカドン！ ドントカドン！
Don-ta-ka-don! Don-ta-ka-don! Don-ta-ka-don!
お肉と野菜をドントカドン☆
Meat and vegetables, don-ta-ka-don☆
サクリンパっ！ サクリンパっ！
Sakurinpa! Sakurinpa!
カラピッチュ！(←揚げ物だって出来ちゃいます！)
Karapitchu! (<- Even fried food is possible!)
ぐとうぐとう だぷだぷだぷ
Simmering, simmering, overflowing...
タリンチュラリン エビのアジ！
Tarantu-larin, shrimp flavor!
はあちゃまクッキング
Haachama Cooking
はーじまっちゃま～～！
It's starting, chama~~!
1. 調べない 調べたやつからサクリンパ！
1. Don't research! Sakurinpa what you researched!
ネットやレシピを見るのは ぜ～ったいダメダメ
Looking at the web or recipes is absolutely NO-NO
2. 測らない 測るのはゴミ！
2. Don't measure! Measuring is trash!
自分量でも作れるのが 一流だぉぉぉ！
Cooking by eye is what makes a professional!
3. はちゃめちゃアレンジ！
3. Crazy arrangements!
最後はオリジナルの隠し味！
Finally, the original secret ingredient!
これは料理の成長物語...！
This is a story of culinary growth...!
はあちゃまカレーは五つ星
Haachama curry is five stars
スパイスマシマシで！
Load it up with spices!
作り方を今教えます
I'll teach you the recipe now
めんどくさいので省きます！
It's a pain, so I'll skip it!
(てめぇ勝手に想像しろ)
(Imagine it yourself, you bastard)
見た目はゴミ でもめちゃ美味し
It looks like trash, but it's super tasty
目指すは世界一！
Aiming for world number one!
※おええぇ...
*Ugh...*
あなたの胃袋掴んじゃう
I'll grab your heart (and stomach)
ぎゅっ。 ぎゅっ。
Gyuu. Gyuu.
はい、あーん♡
Here, say 'ahh'♡
友達減る 見せたら減る
Friends decrease, show them and they decrease
左から2番目にきゅう
Q at the second from the left...
正気で美味しい 完全食
Tasty even if you're sane, Complete Meal
お残しした人だーれだ？
Who's the person who left leftovers?
BAN！ バイ バイ おつるーじゅ！
BAN! Bye bye! Otsu-rouge!
It's only love
もしも願い一つだけ叶うなら
If I could have only one wish
君の側で眠らせて
Let me sleep right next to you
どんな場所でもいいよ
Anywhere is fine
Beautiful world
迷わず君だけを見つめている
I'll look only at you unwaveringly
Beautiful boy
自分の美しさ
Your own beauty...
まだ知らないの
you still don't know it
It's only love
寝ても覚めても
Whether I'm asleep or awake
少年漫画
Shonen manga
夢見てばっか
I'm just dreaming
自分が好きじゃないの
I don't like myself
何が欲しいか分からなくて
Not knowing what I want
ただ欲しがって
I just want it
ぬるい涙が頬を伝う
Lukewarm tears run down my cheeks
言いたいことなんかない
I have nothing I want to say
ただもう一度会いたい
I just want to see you one more time
言いたいこと言えない
I can't say what I want to say
根性無しかもしれない
Maybe I'm a coward
それでいいけど
That's fine, but...
もしも願い一つだけ叶うなら
If I could have only one wish
君の側で眠らせて
Let me sleep right next to you
どんな場所でもいいよ
Anywhere is fine
Beautiful world
迷わず君だけを見つめている
I'll look only at you unwaveringly
Beautiful boy
自分の美しさ
Your own beauty...
まだ知らないの
you still don't know it
It's only love
そんなことでやってみて
Try doing such things,
損したって
even if you lose out
少し経験値上がる
Your experience will go up a bit
新聞はいらない
I don't need the newspaper
肝心なことが載ってない
The important things aren't in there
最近調子どうだい
How've you been lately?
元気にしてるなら
If you're doing well,
別にいいけど
that's fine by me
僕の世界消えるまで
Until my world disappears
会えるなら
If we can meet,
君の側で眠らせて
let me sleep right next to you
どんな場所でも結構
Anywhere is fine
Beautiful world
儚すぎてゆく日の中で
In the days that pass too fleetingly
Beautiful world
自分を信じるしかないね
I've got to believe in myself
もしも願い
If only one wish...
もしも願い一つだけ叶うなら
If only one of my wishes could come true
君の側で眠らせて
Let me sleep by your side
どんな場所でもいいよ
Any place would be fine
Beautiful world
All quartets lead, lead to…? say la-la-la...
All quartets lead, Bird to...? say la-la-la...
やあ また会えたね
Hey, we met again
こんばんは いや こんにちはだっけ?
Good evening, or was it good afternoon?
広いようで 狭いようで
It seems wide, yet it seems narrow
退屈は要らないみたいだね
It seems we don't need boredom
ああ 問題は 依然あって
Ah, problems still exist
頭痛いんだけれど
and they're a headache, but...
少しずつって 言い聞かせて
Telling myself to take it bit by bit
願い事叶えて行きましょうね
Let's go and make our wishes come true
I shall remember I wanna do, I shall remember
拾い集めた 後悔の欠片たちを
The fragments of regret I've gathered up
夜が明ける前に ラベルを貼って 並べてって
Before the night ends, label them and line them up
希望に変える準備を継続中
Currently preparing to turn them into hope
さあ 桜が咲いて散ったその後で
Now, after the cherry blossoms bloom and fall
何が真実なのかは わかるから
I'll know what the truth is
future melody そう 今は奏でて
future melody, yes, play it now
愛が世界救うだなんて
That love will save the world...
僕は信じてないけどね
I don't really believe that, though
今 目の前の君が
Just so that you, right in front of me
明日を生きれるくらいには
can live through tomorrow
ありえない不条理は ぶっ飛ばして行け
Let's blow away all the impossible absurdities
with 喜怒哀楽 余すな必要ないよ
With all our emotions, no need to hold back
嘘つき
You liar
さあ アンプリファーは絶好調
Now, the amplifier is in top shape
エレキギターがうなってる
The electric guitar is roaring
こんなにも歪んでるのに
Even though it's so distorted
心が純粋に求めてる
My heart is purely seeking it
ああ 何回も 何千回も
Ah, time and time again, thousands of times
お望み通り鳴らすよ
I'll play it just as you wish
君が欲しいタイミングで
At the timing you want it
わがままにスイッチを押しましょうか
Shall we selfishly press the switch?
You can reaction, and play it loud, you can reaction
はしゃぎ過ぎてた 青春時代のいろはとか
The basics of my over-excited youth
ホコリ被る前に 選び出して 磨いてって
Before they gather dust, pick them out and polish them
歌に乗っちゃう番狂わせしたい
I want to cause an upset on the wings of song
一斉のせで魔法も使えるよ
Ready, set, go! We can even use magic
君は自由なんだから
Because you are free
止めないで future symphony
Don't stop the future symphony
そう お気に召すまま
Yes, just as you like it
不器用でも混ぜ合わせるよ
Even if it's clumsy, I'll mix it together
この街に響いて行け
Let it echo through this town
ミュージック、歪なるミュージック
Music, distorted music
大丈夫 僕らが試金石
It's okay, we are the touchstone
じゃじゃじゃじゃーん 足りない!
Ta-da! It's not enough!
キック リズムを打て!
Kick, hit the rhythm!
ベース&ギター
Bass and guitar
おまけに僕が歌えば 四重奏
Plus if I sing, it's a quartet
I shall remember I wanna do, I shall remember
忘れない 忘れないよ
I won't forget, I'll never forget
今も大人になっても
Even now, even when I become an adult
だからこの瞬間は楽しませて
So let me enjoy this moment
歌うよ、でたらめでいいよね?
I'll sing it, it's okay if it's nonsense, right?
All quartets lead, lead to…? say la-la-la...
All quartets lead, lead to...? say la-la-la...
桜が
Cherry blossoms...
咲いて散ったそのあとで
Having bloomed and fallen, after that,
何が真実なのかは
What the truth is...
わかるから future melody
I can tell from the future melody.
さあ 今 奏でて
Now, play it out.
世界救うだなんて
As for saving the world and such,
僕は信じてないけどね
I don't really believe in it, though.
今 目の前の君が
But for you, who are right before my eyes now,
明日を生きれるくらいには
To be able to live through tomorrow...
ありえない不条理は
Throw those impossible absurdities...
ぶっ飛ばしていけ
...to the wind!
with 喜怒哀楽
With all your emotions,
余すな全部惜しみなく
Spare nothing, give it your all.
言えないまま
Don't just keep them in,
飲み込むなんて事はよしして
Swallowing it all down is out of the question.
with 喜怒哀楽
With all your emotions,
大丈夫さどこまでも行くだろう
It'll be fine, you'll go wherever you want.
All quartets lead, lead to...? say la-la-la...
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
ふぅー、ということで、ソロパートでした！
Whew! And with that, those were the solo parts!
あれ？みんな、衣装着替えて一緒にいます？
Huh? Everyone, you've changed outfits and are here together?
ずっとここにいたよ。
We were here the whole time.
え、嘘！いたの？
What, no way! You were?
一番近くで見てたよ！
We were watching from the closest spot!
え、そうだったの？
Oh, really?
なんか、確かになんかちょっと今日多いなとか思ったけども。
I did think there were a lot of people today.
ま、ということでですね、ソロパートだったんですけども、
Well, anyway, those were the solo parts,
じゃあちょっと一人ずつね、改めて感想などなどなんですが。
but let's hear everyone's thoughts one by one.
まつりちゃんの「アンデット」。
Starting with Matsuri-chan's "Undead".
はい、「アンデット」ね、やっぱこの雰囲気に合わせて選んだんですけど、
Yes, I chose "Undead" to match this atmosphere,
なんかこの歌詞がすごいMVっぽく出してもらって。
and they displayed the lyrics like a music video.
良かったー！
It was great!
そうなんですよ。カッコ可愛く歌えたかなと思いました。
I think I managed to sing it both coolly and cutely.
そして、はあちゃま！
And next, Haachama!
はい、はあちゃまと一緒に踊りました。
Yes, I danced together with Haachama!
ハート、ハートやばかったね。
The hearts were amazing!
すげえ決まってた。
It looked really sharp.
そして新しく出たね、「めちゃゴミ完全食」。
And then the new one, "Mechagomi Kanzeishoku".
みんなどうだった？
How did everyone like it?
最高！
It was the best!
「めちゃゴミ完全食」っていうゴミカワな曲になっております。
It's a "trash-cute" song called "Mechagomi Kanzeishoku".
たくさん聴いてね。
Please listen to it a lot.
実写入ってたもんね。
It even had live-action footage.
そしてアキちゃん！
And Aki-chan!
はい、アキロゼは、「Vamo」！
Yes, Aki Rosenthal performed "Vamo"!
アキロゼどうだった？
Akiroze, how was it?
いや、結構頑張らせてもらったんだけど。
Well, I worked pretty hard on it.
すごかった！可愛い！
It was amazing! So cute!
進化してたわ。
You've really evolved.
さ、この空間でね、こういう演出をずっとずっとやりたいと思ってたから、
I've always wanted to do this kind of production in this space,
ちょうどね、世界観にも合ってるし、すごく頑張りました。
so it fit the worldview perfectly. I did my best.
さすがだったよ！
You were brilliant!
はい、ありがとう。
Yes, thank you.
はい、最後はね、フブライは一匹だったんですけど、
And finally, while there was only one Fuburai,
なんかスコン部がやたら多かったんですけども。
there sure were a lot of Sukonbu.
はい、白上バンド曲がすごく大好きなので、
I love the Shirakami Band songs so much,
こちらの「桜のあと」歌わせていただきました。
so I sang "Sakura no Ato".
本当にありがとうございます。めちゃめちゃ楽しかったです！
Thank you so much. I had a blast!
ここからは、それぞれ一期生のイメージに合う楽曲を一曲チョイスして
Each of us 1st gen members has chosen a song
全員で歌う、プロデュース曲パートです！
that fits our image for the "Produced Songs" part!
みんな、どんな曲選んだのか、めちゃめちゃ楽しみですね！
I'm so excited to see what songs everyone chose!
はい、まつりはね、まあ王道かなっていう曲を選んだんですけど。
Well, I chose what I'd call a classic song.
はあちゃまはどんな曲？
Haachama, what kind of song is yours?
はあちゃまは、えー、可愛い！可愛くて、仲良しな曲にしました。
Mine is... cute! A cute song about being close friends.
なるほどー。
I see.
アキロゼは？
How about Akiroze?
アキロゼはね、ま、今どき感もありつつ、ま、ちょっとダークなみたいな。
Mine has a modern feel, but it's also a bit dark.
そういう一面もあるんじゃないかなみたいな。
I thought it would show that side of me.
フブちゃんは？
What about Fubu-chan?
白上はですね、一期生だからこそ染みる曲。
For me, it's a song that really hits home for us 1st gen.
あー、いいねー！
Oh, that's nice!
染みる曲でございます。
It's a very touching song.
皆さんもね、コメントなどで予想して、お楽しみに！
Everyone, please try to guess in the comments!
じゃあ、いきますよ。それではプロデュースパート、せーの！
Here we go. The Produced Part starts... ready?
スタート！！
Start!!
好きか嫌いかの人間だ
I'm the type who either likes or dislikes things.
どちらかと言えば好きでした
If I had to say, I liked it.
乗りかかった船 止めちゃうほど
Not so much that I'd stop a boat I've already boarded,
零れていないよ わかるでしょ
I haven't lost my head, you know?
予想外なのも 結構で
Unexpected things are fine too.
虎視眈々 続く人生 案外
This life that continues so watchfully is quite...
行き先なんて 二の次なんです
The destination is only secondary.
好き嫌い 突き勝てるでしょ
I can overcome my likes and dislikes, right?
アクセルしか踏まないよ
I'll only step on the gas!
止まり方なんて
Like how to stop
必要ないって
There's no need for that
ドリフターじゃない
I'm not a drifter
涙もエンタメになる
Even tears become entertainment
カメラ止めんなよ
Don't stop the camera
ハイッ！
Hi!
不甲斐ない私でもずっと
Even for a pathetic me, I've always...
歩いてきた道がある
had a path that I've walked.
つまり とても良いことなど
In short, something like a very good thing...
何もなかったんだよ
there was nothing at all.
私 混乱上々 いつだって
I'm in high spirits of confusion, always...
ここが最前線さ
the front line is right here.
最後まで目を離さないで
Don't take your eyes off me until the end.
そりゃ 私だって
Well, even for me...
悩みの一つや二つはありますよ
I have a worry or two.
眠れない 夜の旅 彷徨う
Wandering through a sleepless night's journey.
選択肢のスタンプ
The stamps of choices...
バックアップなんてしたくないよ
I don't want to make a backup.
オートセーブ切って 挑む価値
Turning off auto-save, it's worth the challenge.
リアルなんだ
It's real.
緊張を 鼓動に変える 瞬きすんなよ
Turning tension into a heartbeat, don't blink.
変わんない私だからきっと
Because it's a me that won't change, surely...
繋いできた夢がある
there's a dream that I've connected.
つまり ろくでもないことなど
In short, something like a worthless thing...
何もなかったんだよ
there was nothing at all.
私 逆境上々 いつだって
I'm in high spirits in adversity, always...
今が最高潮さ
right now is the peak.
最後まで手を離さないで
Don't let go of my hand until the end.
普通じゃなくて 特別じゃない
Not ordinary, and not special.
代わりのいない 僕らだから
Because we are irreplaceable.
止まない雨を 明けない夜を
Through the rain that won't stop, the night that won't break...
癒えない傷を 越えたんでしょ
we've overcome the wounds that won't heal, right?
不甲斐ない私でもずっと
Even for a pathetic me, I've always...
歩いてきた道がある
had a path that I've walked.
つまり どうでもいいことなど
In short, something like a trivial thing...
何もなかったんだよ
there was nothing at all.
私 混乱上々 いつだって
I'm in high spirits of confusion, always...
ここが最前線さ
the front line is right here.
最後まで目を離さないで
Don't take your eyes off me until the end.
最後まで私負けないから
Because I won't lose until the end.
出会った日の輝き
The sparkle of the day we met...
飾ってた偽りも
even the falsehoods we adorned.
歌い出した憧れも
And the admiration we started singing about...
カメラ止めんなよ
don't stop the camera.
空回ったエネルギー
The energy that spun its wheels...
輝くこのステージで
on this shining stage.
重なる物語
Stories that overlap...
瞬きすんなよ
don't blink.
シタイから！
Because I want to!
シタイなら！
If you want to!
シタイとき！
When you want to!
シタイでしょ！？
You want to, right!?
いっしょに！
Together!
わたしたちはここにいます！
We are here!
ここには夢がちゃんとある
Here, there's a dream for sure.
フレンドなら 友達でしょ
If we're friends, we're friends, right?
「そうだ！」
"That's right!"
「すき」って言ってみた
I tried saying "I love you".
だいすきっ
I love you so much!
放課後なら 当たり前のこと
After school, it's the natural thing.
さあさ集まれ こっそり帰るな
Come on, gather round, don't sneak home.
部活動だね 活動しちゃうね
It's club activities, let's get active!
遊んでるんじゃありませんっ
We're not just playing!
「ただいま」ってあの子が言うよ
That girl says "I'm home".
「おかえりー」
"Welcome back!"
みんなでいれば大丈夫
If we're all together, we'll be fine.
「部っ！」
"Club!"
エビバディセイ！
Everybody say!
ともだちでいよーね
Let's be friends forever!
シタイから！
Because I want to!
シタイなら！
If you want to!
シタイでしょ！？
You want to, right!?
だいすきっ はいっ！
I love you so much! Yes!
わたしたちは楽しんでる
We are having fun!
24時間 はしゃいでる
Frolicking for 24 hours.
屋上に 真っ赤な太陽
A crimson sun on the rooftop.
かなり叫んでみた！
I tried shouting quite a lot!
「元気でーす！」
"I'm doing great!"
わたしたちはここにいます！
We are here!
ここには夢がちゃんとある
Here, there's a dream for sure.
フレンドなら 友達でしょ
If we're friends, we're friends, right?
「そうだ！」
"That's right!"
「すき」って言ってみた
I tried saying "I love you".
だいすきっ
I love you so much!
キンコンカンコン 下校タイム
Ding-dong-ding-dong, time to go home.
いいえ わたしたち まだ帰らない
No, we're not going home yet.
「やだよー」
"No way!"
部活動だよ 活躍しちゃうよ
It's club activities, we're gonna be active!
新入部員 募集中っ！
Recruiting new members!
ごめんね ばっちり咲くよ
Sorry, we'll bloom perfectly.
ケンカするほど ほにゃらら
The more you fight, the more blah blah...
ネバギバアップ 最強になれるね
Never give up, we can become the strongest.
シタイから！
Because I want to!
シタイなら！
If you want to!
シタイとき！
When you want to!
シタイでしょ！？
You want to, right!?
いっしょに！
Together!
わたしたちは経験する
We will experience it.
食べて眠って賢くなる
Eating and sleeping to become wiser.
校庭に 涼風吹いて
A cool breeze blowing in the schoolyard...
大きく手を振る
waving my hand big.
「また明日ねー！」
"See you tomorrow!"
わたしたちはここにいます！
We are here!
ここには夢がちゃんとある
Here, there's a dream for sure.
フレンドなら 友達でしょ
If we're friends, we're friends, right?
「そうだ！」
"That's right!"
「すき」って言ってみた
I tried saying "I love you".
だいすきっ
I love you so much!
「すき」って言ってみた
I tried saying "I love you"
すき
I love you
みんながここに集まれば
When everyone gathers here,
がっこうは特別になる
School becomes special.
今日が終わっても明日も
Even when today ends, tomorrow too,
笑顔で会えるね！
We can meet with a smile!
あたしたちはここにいます！
We are right here!
ここには夢がちゃんとある
Our dreams are properly here.
フレンドならともだちでしょ
If we're friends, we're friends, right?
だいすき ありがとう！
I love you, thank you!
どうしてすぐ知ってしまうの
Why do you know it immediately?
共振で苦しんでし罵倒
Suffering from resonance, I curse
Q. 更新で降る隕石抹消可？
Q. Can the meteorite falling in the update be erased?
悪くない
Not bad
興味ねえ救い派手感動
I'm not interested in salvation, flashy excitement
常備ねえ薬食べBAD
I don't have medicine on hand, taking it is BAD
Q. 超酷えフル見た目暗号化？
Q. Is the super-brutal full appearance encrypted?
金による...
Because of money...
常識ねえ狂いっぱで乱闘
Fighting while out of our minds without common sense
放置ゲーする陰キャラでバンド
Forming a band with introverts playing idle games
Q. 送信で苦しいダメCancelは？
Q. Can the painful 'Cancel' on transmission be done?
草生える
LOL
どうしてすぐ見てしまうの どうしてすぐ言ってしまうの
Why do I look right away? Why do I say it right away?
どうしてすぐ壊れちゃうかな
I wonder why it breaks so easily
近未来しか勝たん
The near future is the best
ショッピングモールの現代コンピュー
Modern computers in the shopping mall
庶民の死とか加担
Complicit in the death of commoners
モンティホールの経費でピンボール
Playing pinball on Monty Hall's expenses
オイルマッサージ100分コース足湯付き
100-minute oil massage with a foot bath
柚子を添えて
With a side of yuzu
どうしてこんな目に
Why am I in this situation?
興味がないこと本気じゃないもの全部後回しで
Putting aside everything that doesn't interest me or I'm not serious about
知ってることは知らんぷり 私は終わってる
Pretending not to know what I know, I'm a mess
恥ずかしい過去知ってる奴らの記憶消させて
Let me erase the memories of those who know my embarrassing past
迷惑かけてごめんってば ねえ誰か助けて
I said I'm sorry for being a nuisance, hey, someone help me
妄信ですぐ惹かれちゃうの 狂信ですぐ惹かれちゃうの
I'm immediately drawn in by blind faith, immediately drawn in by fanaticism
知りたくない 知りたくない 知りたくない
I don't want to know, I don't want to know, I don't want to know
もう見えねえすぐ惹かれSAD
I can't see anymore, immediately drawn in and SAD
常動で狂いたてMAD
Going MAD with habitual movements
行きたくない 行きたくない 生きたくない
I don't want to go, I don't want to go, I don't want to live
ばーいばい
Bye-bye
臨時休業 洗濯ボール
Temporary closure, laundry balls
ナイチンゲールの配置ゲーム
Nightingale's placement game
名刺交換の名シーン
The famous business card exchange scene
借金ボウルでチンチロハイボール
Playing Chinchirorin for highballs in a debt bowl
温泉旅行３泊４日食事付き
Hot spring trip, 4 days and 3 nights with meals included
早く行きてえ
I want to go soon
共感性羞恥
Vicarious embarrassment
うそとかそうとか忙しくて眠れないわ今日も
Lies and such, I'm too busy to sleep again today
誰か早く殴って気絶させてくれよ
Someone, punch me quickly and knock me out
人生キャンセルキャンセル界隈 ぼんやりとした不安
In the circles of cancelling life, a vague anxiety
私のせい 私が悪いよそうだよ
It's my fault, I'm the bad one, that's right
興味が出ても本気でやっても全部空回りで
Even if I get interested or try my best, it's all in vain
知らないくせに嘘つき 私は終わってる
Lying despite not knowing, I'm a mess
恥ずかしい過去知ってる奴らの記憶消させて
Let me erase the memories of those who know my embarrassing past
迷惑かけてごめんってば ねえ誰か助けて
I said I'm sorry for being a nuisance, hey, someone help me
迷惑かけてごめんってば ねえ誰か許して
I said I'm sorry for being a nuisance, hey, someone forgive me
絶対 アイドル辞めないで（ずっと）
Absolutely, never stop being an Idol (Ever)
輝いてる君を見たい
I want to see you shining
もう ずっとずっとずっと
Already, forever and ever
ステージにいて
Be on the stage
私がもし君のとこ 離れたなら
If I were to leave your side
君はちょっと寂しくなるかな
Would you feel a little lonely?
いじわる 考える
Teasing, thinking
好きな人がいるのなら 内緒にして ねえ
If you have someone you like, keep it a secret, okay?
ねえ 神様は将来と指輪を どこかに隠してる
Hey, God is hiding our future and rings somewhere
君の「好き」に合わせたんだ 髪の色
I matched my hair color to what you like
私の中 君だけで 過剰摂取中毒へ
With only you inside me, I'm heading towards an overdose addiction
責任とってね 大好きです
Take responsibility, okay? I love you
絶対 アイドル辞めないで（ずっと）
Absolutely, never stop being an Idol (Ever)
優しい目も 真面目な...
Your kind eyes, your serious...
ステージにいて
Stay on the stage
私がもし君のとこ 離れたなら
If I ever left your side...
絶対空で輝いて
Definitely shine in the sky
星は街じゃ輝かないの
Stars don't shine in the city
眩しい君が 世界一だよ
The dazzling you are the best in the world!
好きだー！
I love you!
君の夢は 何ですか？ 教えてほしい
What is your dream? I want you to tell me
その夢がアイドルじゃなくても 覚悟はしてるから
Even if that dream isn't to be an idol, I'm prepared for it.
星のいない空 それが当たり前で
A sky with no stars, that's only natural...
暗い道に目が慣れずに 踏み出すのも怖かった
My eyes not used to the dark road, I was afraid to take a step forward.
そんな時やっと見えた光
In those times, I finally saw a light.
絶対君は歌ってて
Definitely keep on singing
ただのエゴと分かってても
Even knowing it's just my ego...
キラキラ衣装 似合うよ
The sparkling outfit suits you
絶対大きなステージで
Definitely on a big stage
一列で前で感じたい
I want to feel it in the front row
今日の歌い方 なんか好きだなぁ
The way you sing today, I kind of like it.
君の努力 私の愛
Your effort, my love
成り立つこの関係は
this relationship consists of...
強くてもろいの
it's strong yet fragile.
星の幸せを願った
I wished for the stars' happiness.
だけど... でもね
But... you know...
だって君はアイドルよ
Because you are an idol.
ずっと
Always
初めて目が合った日から
Since the day our eyes first met,
今日も明日も君ばかりだ
Today and tomorrow, it's always you.
絶対アイドル辞めないで（ずっと）
Absolutely, never stop being an idol (always)
これは報われないおとぎ話
This is an unrewarded fairy tale
恋よりももっと好きだ
I love you more than love itself
魔法よどうか 解けないままで
Magic, please stay unbroken.
イェーイ！ はーい！
Yeah! Hi!
と言うことで、ホロプロプロデュース曲パート1でした！
So, that was the Holo-Pro Produce songs part 1!
どうだったかなー？
How was it?
選曲1曲目はまず「キラー」でございました！
The first song chosen was "Killer"!
いやめっちゃ良い曲なのに、めっちゃちょっと激しいダンスだったと思うんですけども
It's such a good song, but I think the dance was a bit intense...
いやもうなんか本当にこの曲聴いて、絶対1期生これだろうっていうね
Really, listening to this song, I thought "This is definitely 1st Gen"...
思いながらちょっと歌い分けとかもね、させていただいたんですけども
and I did the line distribution too.
本当に沁みた
It really touched me.
沁みたでしょ？ そう、沁みたでしょ？
It touched you, right? Yeah, right?
そうそう、我々は常に最前線と言うことで
Yeah yeah, we are always on the front lines.
やったー！ いやもうね、1期生これからも頑張っていこう、最後まで目を離すんじゃないぞ！
Yay! Let's keep doing our best as 1st Gen, don't take your eyes off us until the end!
辞めるな、辞めるなよ
Don't quit, don't quit!
そしてそして、次が？
And then, next is?
はい、アキロゼのテトリスをやらせていただきました
Yes, I performed Aki-Rose's "Tetris".
テテテテトリス！ いやこれはね、可愛かったからいつかじゃあみんなでやってみたいなと思ったの
Te-te-te-tetris! This was cute, so I thought I'd like to try it with everyone someday.
で、グループのこうフォーメーションとかをぐるぐるして...
And doing the group formations and stuff...
なんかしたけれども、それをでちょっと頑張ってもらっちゃった
I had everyone work hard on that.
やったー！ ありがとうみんな頑張ってくれて
Yay! Thank you everyone for working hard.
表情やばかった
The expressions were crazy.
まあなんか我々はだいぶムスッとした気がしますね
Well, I feel like we were looking quite grumpy.
まあそんな一面も愛してよと言うことで、はい、お願いします
Well, please love that side of us too.
そして？
And?
はい、はあちゃまは「ふれんどしたーい」！ フレンド...したかった！
Yes, Haachama did "Friend Shitai"! I wanted to be... friends!
と言うことで選びました。
So I chose it.
あの後ろの映像でね、思い出アルバムみたいに...
With the video in the back like a memory album...
良かった、モニター割れてなくて良かったってなりました
I'm glad, I was like "I'm glad the monitor didn't break".
割れてないですー
It's not broken!
はい、そして？
Yes, and?
まつり最後に「絶対アイドル辞めないで」！
Matsuri, finally, "Zettai Idol Yamenai de"!
いやこれはね、まあまつりのエゴだったとしてもみんなにはアイドルでいてほしいなという気持ちで選ばせていただきましたよ
Yeah, this one, even if it's Matsuri's ego, I chose it with the feeling that I want everyone to stay as idols.
この曲もなんか1期でやるとやっぱ沁みたね
Doing this song with 1st Gen really touched me too.
やっぱ7年目だからね、余計に良かったです
Since it's the 7th year, it was even better.
お、そしてこのパートが終わったと言うことで...
Oh, and since this part has ended...
さぁ！
So!
じゃそろそろ、
Then, I think it's about time...
ハッシュタグの秘密を教えちゃおうかな！
...I tell you the secret of the hashtag!
なんとこのハッシュタグなんですが、
Wait, what's this hashtag? It's actually...
新曲のタイトルになってます！
...the title of our new song!
ということで、タイトルは、
And so, the title is...
「電脳ぴゅあ推し大宣言」！
'Dennou Pure Oshi Dai Sengen'!
おぉ！これは一体どんな曲なんだ！
Whoa! What kind of song is this?!
一体どんな感じなんだろうなー。
I wonder what it's like!
楽しみー！
I'm excited!
いやぁドキドキでございますけども、
I'm heart-pounding, but...
ぴゅあ推し大宣言ってことは、
Pure Oshi Dai Sengen means...
なんか、あれ？みんなの曲ってことかな？ファンのみんなの曲？
...is it everyone's song? Our fans' song?
おぉ！そういうことか！
Oh! Is that so?
推してくれてるよな？
You're supporting us, right?
推してくれてるよな？っていう曲なのか？
Is it a song about you supporting us?
そう、みんな、この配信見てくれてるみんなが、
Yes! Everyone watching this stream...
私たちのこと「推し」だよね？
...you support us, don't you?
え？
What?
まさか、他の人によそ見なんかしてないよね？
You're not looking at others, right?
えー？！
What?!
四六時中、私たちのこと考えてるよね？
You're thinking about us all day long, right?
え、１期生が推しだって宣言してくれるよなー！！
You'll declare that the 1st Generation is your 'oshi', right?!
ということで、それでは聴いてください。
Alright then, please listen.
１期生の新曲。せーの！
1st Generation's new song. Ready, set...
「電脳ぴゅあ推し大宣言」！
'Dennou Pure Oshi Dai Sengen'!
は〜い、これから配信始めるよ！
Hey, I'm starting the stream now!
みんな観てる？
Is everyone watching?
今回はコラボ配信！
This time it's a collab stream!
あれ？あれれ〜？コメントの熱量、なんだか少なくない？
Huh? Huh huh? Isn't the heat of the comments a bit low?
まだまだ足りないっ！こんなの〜！
It's still not enough! Like this!
推し変は許しませんっ！！
Changing 'oshi' is not allowed!!
「わ・た・し」だけに尽くしてね
Devote yourself only to me
わたしだけに一途
A single-minded devotion only to me
単推しじゃなきゃヤダヤダヤダ
If you're not single-minded, no, no, no!
拗ねちゃうぞ
I'll get sulky!
他の子にちょろちょろダメです
Dallying with other girls is a no-no
よそ見をしたらプンプンめっ！
If you look away, boom boom! No!
めらめらメンヘラっプ
Burning with menhera-love
ほっぺふくらまし にらめっこしましょ
Puffing out my cheeks, let's have a staring contest
あっ ぷっぷっ ぷいっ！
Poof! Poof! Boo!
フブキ様も可愛いっでしょ！
Fubuki-sama is also cute, right?!
目移りはダメ！ほんとイヤイヤ
Being fickle is no good! I really hate it
いつも観て観て わたし待ってる
Always watch me, watch me, I'm waiting
あなたが推してくれてる愛情の全部が
All the affection you give me as your 'oshi'
わたしをささえる栄養素
is the nutrition that supports me
LOVE YOU LOVE YOU しろくじちゅう ちゅっちゅ
Love you, love you, all day long, chu chu
ねえ とっても とっても とっても
Hey, I want you to love me...
とっても 愛してほしい
...very, very, very, very much!
HAPPY HAPPY びゅあ最高級はゆ
Happy happy, the supreme 'oshi'
ほら やっぱり やっぱり やっぱり やっぱり
Hey, as I thought, as I thought, as I thought, as I thought
はっきり はっきり はっきり はっきり
clearly, clearly, clearly, clearly!
わかってんでしょ？ ぴゅぴゅあ振リ切って
You know it, right? Break through the limit!
ぴこぴこキモチのバロメーターも超上がる
The meter of my feelings is rising high!
ぴゅぴゅあ振リ切って
Break through the limit!
神推し 神推し 大推し
Kami-oshi! Kami-oshi! Dai-oshi!
もう本当に本当に本当に本当に
Really, really, really, really
わかってね！！
Understand, okay?!
おーい、みんな！ここまでついてこれてる？
Hey, everyone! Can you keep up so far?
この後もこの調子で行くよー！！
Let's keep going with this momentum!!
うりゃおい！うりゃおい！うりゃおい！うりゃおい！
Uri-oi! Uri-oi! Uri-oi! Uri-oi!
ちょっと待って、なんで他の子ほめるの？
Wait a minute! Why are you praising other girls?
よそ見疑惑発令中
Suspicion of looking away currently occurring
わたし以外も気になってるでしょ！
You're interested in someone other than me too, right!
ありえないよ ありえない！
Unbelievable! Unbelievable!
ぺっぺ 他の子にちょちょちょっとだけ
Pe-pe! Dallying with other girls just a little bit
よそ見したよね！？うそマジ無理です
You looked away, didn't you?! Liar! Truly impossible.
ぴゅあ推し信者 わたし押すんじゃ？
Pure 'oshi' believer, support me!
指切りしてよ 針千本×1000
Pinky swear! Swallow a thousand needles!
心変わりしたらほんとに
If you have a change of heart, really...
拗ねる、怒る、泣いちゃうからね！！
...I'll sulk, get angry, and cry!!
推し変はしてないね
You're not changing your 'oshi', right?
「わ・た・し」だけに尽くしてる！！！
Devote yourself only to me!!!
残念ほらコメントが愛に溢れている
Look! The comments are overflowing with love!
瀕死のHPみるみる回復
Recovering my critical HP in no time
チド級レベルなパワーチャージ
Highest level of support! Power charge
ごめごめごめちょ ごめごめごめちょ
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry!
LOVE YOU LOVE YOU しろくじちゅう ちゅっちゅ
Love you, love you, all day long, chu chu
ねえ いっぱい いっぱい いっぱい
Hey, I want you to love me...
いっぱい 愛してほしい
...very, very, very, very much!
HAPPY HAPPY びゅあ最高級はゆ
Happy happy, the supreme 'oshi'
もううっとり うっとり うっとり うっとり
Being entranced, entranced, entranced, entranced!
にっこり にっこり にっこり にっこり
Smiling, smiling, smiling, smiling!
わたしのたのめ日々、日々、
For my sake, everyday, everyday,
お仕事に励んでくれて
working hard at your 'oshi' duties
ありがとう
Thank you
ぴゅぴゅあひたすらに
Break through the limit!
神推し 神推し 大推し
Kami-oshi! Kami-oshi! Dai-oshi!
ぜったい ぜったい ぜったい ぜったい
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely, absolutely
お願いね！！！
Please!!!
このこのこのこの
Kono kono kono kono
んー このこのこのこの
Hmm! Kono kono kono kono
このこのこのこのー！
Kono kono kono kono!
銀河の果てまで (oshi shite hoshii)
To the ends of the galaxy, support me!
ということで新曲でしたー！
And so, that was our new song!
可愛いきょくたったねー！
It was such a cute song!
めっちゃ可愛いし、なんかね、「推し」って感じで
It was super cute, and felt like 'oshi'!
ぜひ歌ったり踊ったりいっぱい楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいなという...
I hope everyone will sing and dance to it a lot!
...一曲になってるんだけど、どうだった？
...it's that kind of song, but how was it?
いやーもう、やっぱ楽しいね、この曲ね！
It's so fun, this song!
ぜんぜん楽しい！
Super fun!
全体的には結構、白上のど趣味な曲シークレットさせてもらったんだけど、
It's a song that reflects Shirakami's hobbies quite a bit...
なんか今回...
...I got to make it, but...
この曲聴いた時に
When I heard this song,
あ、これこれ、ちょっとまつりちゃんにね、ちょっと頑張ってもらおうかなってとこで
I thought, "This is it! I should have Matsuri-chan give it her all here."
セリフのとことかさ、ちょっとね、まつりちゃんに
For the spoken lines and such, I wanted Matsuri-chan to do them.
あ、そう、歌い分けをフブキが
Ah, right, Fubuki handled the part distribution.
そうそう。なんかちょっと決めっぽいところはまつりちゃんかなと思って。
Yeah, yeah. I thought the cool, decisive parts should be Matsuri-chan's.
あそこみんなよく噛まなかったね。
Everyone did well not to stumble over those lines.
アキロゼ、セクシーだったね。
Aki-Rose, you were sexy.
あ、良かった！
Oh, good!
私、ここ好き。ペンペンってね。
I like this part. The "pen-pen" part.
お尻叩いてね。めっちゃ可愛かった。
Slapping the butt. It was so cute.
まつりちゃんに銃で撃たれてた時。バーン！
When Matsuri-chan shot me with a gun. Bang!
あれ可愛かったです。
That was cute.
ほい、そんなこの曲は？この曲が？なんと？
Now then, what about this song? This song is...?
この後 21時15分から、こちらの公式チャンネルで
Following this, from 21:15, on this official channel,
先ほど歌わせていただきました新曲「電脳ぴょあ推し大宣言」の
the MV for our new song "Cyber Pure Oshi Daiseigen", which we just performed,
MVが出ちゃいまーす！
will be released!
めちゃめちゃ可愛い映像になってますので、ぜひそちらもチェックしてくださいね！
It's a very cute video, so please be sure to check it out!
さて、ではここからは告知タイムです！
Now then, from here, it's announcement time!
今回のグッズは「hololive 1st Generation Anniversary Parade」！
This time's merchandise is the "hololive 1st Generation Anniversary Parade"!
こちら5月30日からカートオープンされてます！
The cart has been open for these since May 30th!
皆さんチェックしてくれてるとは思いますが、内容見てみましょう！
I'm sure you've all checked them, but let's look at the contents!
はい、まずキービジュアルはオットン先生に描いていただきました！
Yes, first, the key visual was drawn by Otton-sensei!
今年のホロ全体での周年グッズのテーマは「パレード」！
The theme for this year's Hololive anniversary goods is "Parade"!
その中でも我々1期生はマーチング隊です！
And within that, we 1st Gen members are a marching band!
ではでは、一個ずつグッズ見ていきましょうかね。こちら！
Now then, let's look at the goods one by one. Here!
まずはですね、「プレミアムアクリル色紙」！
First is the "Premium Acrylic Shikishi"!
こちら複製サインとロゴが箔押しで入ってます！
This has reproduced signatures and the logo embossed in foil!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next is this!
「オフィシャルホロカスリーブ Anniversary Parade 1期生ver.」！
"Official Holoka Sleeves Anniversary Parade 1st Gen Ver."!
ホロカが入ります！カードもスリーブも1期生です。お買い上げください！
These fit Holoka cards! Both the cards and sleeves are 1st Gen. Please buy them!
そして次はこちら！お、まつりちゃん行ってもらおうかな。
And next is this! Oh, I'll let Matsuri-chan take this one.
はい！「アクリルスタンド」！
Yes! "Acrylic Stands"!
今回のキービジュアルの衣装がアクリルスタンドになりますよ！
The outfits from this key visual will become acrylic stands!
プレミアムアクリル色紙に比べて、それぞれ表情が異なっちゃいますよ！
Compared to the Premium Acrylic Shikishi, each one has a different expression!
はい、こんな感じですね！
Yes, it's like this!
そして最後はアキロゼ！
And finally, Aki-Rose!
はい、なんと「記念メダル」出ちゃいます！
Yes, a "Commemorative Medal" is coming out!
こちらなんとケースと巾着がついて豪華な仕様になっておりまして、
This comes with a case and a drawstring bag for a luxurious specification,
1期生ごとにデザインが異なっているので、ぜひコレクションしたくなるアイテムです。
and since the design differs for each member, it's an item you'll want to collect.
タレントカラーと名前も入っているので、ぜひゲットしてね！
It also includes the talent's color and name, so please get one!
さて、こちらのグッズなんですが、受注期間が、えーと...
Now then, regarding these goods, the order period is...
5月30日金曜日から今月6月30日
from Friday, May 30th, until this month, June 30th,
月曜日までなので、皆さん忘れずにご購入ください！
which is a Monday, so everyone, please don't forget to purchase them!
以上、周年のグッズ告知でした！
That's all for the anniversary goods announcement!
そして今ハアチャマが、あ、何、何が？
And now Haachama is... Oh, what is it?
そしてなんとまだある！次はメンバー個別の告知タイムです！
And there's actually more! Next is the individual member announcement time!
一個ずつで、まつりちゃんから！
One by one, starting with Matsuri-chan!
はい！じゃあまつりは周年グッズの告知にしますよ！
Yes! Then Matsuri will announce my anniversary goods!
この後 21時30分からまつりの個人の周年グッズが出ちゃいますので、
After this, from 21:30, my individual anniversary goods will be released,
ぜひぜひ買ってください！超可愛いイラストです！
so please, please buy them! The illustrations are super cute!
そしてはあちゃま！
And next, Haachama!
はい！はあちゃまはこちら！ドドン！
Yes! Haachama's is this! Boom!
「めちゃゴ三完全食」！
"Mecha Gomi Perfect Meal"!
本日の0時から各種配信サービスでもリリースされるのでお楽しみに！
It'll be released on various streaming services from midnight today, so look forward to it!
6周年グッズも...
Also 6th anniversary goods...
あります！明日ですよ！6周年？6周年？あれ？
We have them! It's tomorrow! 6th? 6th? Wait?
あ、間違えた。7周年グッズは...
Oh, I messed up. The 7th anniversary goods...
7周年グッズもお楽しみに！8日、8日だよ！
Please look forward to the 7th anniversary goods too! On the 8th!
超豪華なものになっております！
They are super luxurious!
はい、白上です！
Yes, I'm Shirakami!
白上もですね、グッズが出るんですけども、
Shirakami also has goods coming out,
こちらはですね、6月3日に発売予定でございます！
and these are scheduled for release on June 3rd!
グッズの詳細などは良ければ6月3日の配信お楽しみに！
For details on the goods, please look forward to the stream on June 3rd!
そして最後、アキちゃん！
And finally, Aki-chan!
はい、はい、はい、はい！
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
アキロゼの、なんと！
From Akirose, guess what!
2024かな？自分の生誕祭の時にお披露目しました
Was it 2024? I first performed it at my birthday celebration...
ミュージカル、ブレーメンの曲がついに初配信になりました！
...and the 'Bremen' musical song is finally getting its first release!
やったー！
Yay!
なります！この後、24時リリース予定なので、
It is! It's scheduled for release at 24:00 tonight, so...
ぜひいっぱい聴いたり、歌ってみたり
...please listen to it a lot, try singing it...
踊ってみたりして楽しんでもらえたらなと思ってます。
...or even dancing to it and just have a great time.
あと、ミュージックビデオとしてね
Also, as a music video...
そのミュージカル部分だけ切り取ったものも上げようと思ってるので
...I'm planning to upload just the musical segment separately...
アキロゼのチャンネルもぜひ見てください。
...so please check out Akirose's channel too!
はい！以上、告知タイムでしたー！
Alright! That's the end of the announcement time!
ということでですね、7周年迎えて
So, as we reach our 7th anniversary...
え、8周年ですか？明日から。
...wait, is it our 8th year starting tomorrow?
えー！？はやーい！
Whaaat?! So fast!
ということは、あのちびっこに例えると
Which means, if we compare ourselves to kids...
中学2年生。
...we're second-year middle schoolers.
我々は中2！中学2年生になったー！
We're eighth graders! We've become middle schoolers!
封印が解けるような。
It's like a seal being broken.
眩しい！これ以上解き放たれたらまずい！
So bright! It'll be bad if we're unleashed any further!
どうなっちゃうぜー。
What's going to happen to us?
これからもノンビリやっていく一期生ではございますけども
The 1st gen will keep going at our own pace, but...
これからも楽しく活動していきますので
...we'll continue our activities happily...
皆様よろしくお願いします！
...so we look forward to your continued support!
はい、では、それではですね
Alright then...
またそれぞれの配信でお会いしましょう。
...we'll see you all again in our respective streams.
せーの、バイバーイ！
Ready, set... Bye-bye!